A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Commission on Water Quality, 1973-1977; 9; 56 Cubic Feet 56 record cartons
  - Speeches - Staff (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - Speeches - Awards to NAR (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Contracts - Alphabetical and Numerical Listing; Inventory & Status; Contract Releases; Publications List (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Contracts - Abt Associates (River Basin: Merrimack) (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Contracts - Abt Associates (Social Impacts) (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Contracts - Academy of Natural Sciences, Philadelphia (Env. water sites) (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Contracts - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Contracts - American Public Works Association (On Needs Survey) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - Contracts - American Water Works Association Research Foundation (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - Contracts - Arthur D. Little, Inc. (2-Regional) (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Contracts - Association of Metropolitan Sewerage Agencies (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Contracts - Atlantic Scientific (Environmental) (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Contracts - Battelle Memorial Institute (2-Economic) (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Contracts - Bernard Johnson, Inc. (Regional) (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Contracts - Betz Environmental Engineers, Inc. (Regional) (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Contracts - Beychock, Milton R. (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Contracts - Black, Crow & Eidsness (Urban Runoff) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Contracts - Boeing Computer Services, Inc. (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Contracts - Bureau of National Affairs - Legal Study (Institutional) (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Contracts - Burt, Dr. Oscar R. (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Contracts - University of California (Irrigated Agriculture) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Contracts - Catalytic, Inc. (Organic Chemicals) (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Contracts - Center for Environment & Man, Inc. (Economic and Social) (Environmental) (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Contracts - Coastal Ecosystems Management, Inc. (Environmental Water Site) (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Contracts - The Conference Board (Economic) (2) (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Contracts - CONSAD Research Corp (Economic, SEAS) (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Contracts - Control Data Corp (Economic Impact; SEAS; SEAS III System Integration) (2) (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Contracts - Cook, Howard L. - Consultant $10,000 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Contracts - Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport - River Basin: Lake Erie - $285,000 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Contracts - Dames & Moore, Inc. - River Basin: Kanawha - $225,000 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Contracts - Dames & Moore, Inc. - River Basin: Ohio - $211,000 (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Contracts - Data Resources, Inc. - State / Local Finances - $69,600 (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - Contracts - Development Planning & Research Association - Economic Impacts (Agriculture Industry) - $175,000 (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - Contracts - Development Planning & Research Association - Feedlots - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Contracts - David M. Dornbosch & Co. - Economic Impact - Property Valuation - $140,000 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Contracts - Downing, Donald L. - Consultant - Fruits and Vegetables - $2500 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Contracts - Electronic Data Systems - First Overview (Ross Perot) - $75,000 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Contracts - Energy & Environmental Analysis Inc. - Institutional: Permits - $125,000 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Contracts - Energy Resources Co. Inc. - Institutional: Monitoring - $71,150 (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - Contracts - Engineering-Science, Inc. - Ocean Disposal - $14,115 (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - Contracts - Engineering-Science, Inc. - Austin - Petroleum & Refining - $168,000 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - Contracts - Environmental Analysts, Inc. - Environmental Site (Chicago) - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Contracts - Environmental Associates - Fruits & Vegetables Industry - $182,000 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Contracts - Environmental Dynamics, Inc. - Environmental Site: Utah - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Contracts - Environmental Law Institute - Institutional: Enforcement - $127,500 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Contracts - Environmental Quality Systems - Intermedia Transfer - $230,000 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Contracts - Fisher, Anthony - Consultant - $2,500 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Contracts - Florida State University - Economic Impact (Coastal Area Fisheries) - $107,914 (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Contracts - GKY Assoc. - Regional: Evaluation of Reports - Kanawha & Ohio - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Contracts - GKY Assoc. - Environmental Water Site - $15,433 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - Contracts - Hammer, Siler & George Associates - River Basin: Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola - $200,000 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - Contracts - Hartley, David K. - Consultant - Institutional "Doers" - $12,000 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Contracts - Haskell, Elizabeth - Consultant - Institutional - $2,000 (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Contracts - Hazen & Sawyer - New York City Pulp and Paper - $173,000 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - Contracts - Human Resource Planning - Social Impact Site Studies - $42,230 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Contracts - Inerfield, Arthur J. & Assoc. - Institutional Assistance - $5,000 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Contracts - Hydroscience, Inc. - Environmental Site Analysis - $56,115 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Contracts - The Institute of Ecology - $131,552 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - Contracts - Inter-industry Economic Research Fund (SEAS) - $15,000 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - Contracts - International Research & Technology Corp. - Economic Impact - Chemicals Industry - $192,500 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Contracts - International Research & Technology - Economic Impact - SEAS Technology Change and Inside Expansion - $65,000 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Contracts - Iowa State: Center for Agricultural & Rural Development - Economic Impacts: Irrigated Agriculture - $41,000 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Contracts - King, A. Thomas - Consultant - $2,000 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - Contracts - Klashman, Lester A. - Consultant - $1,000 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - Contracts - Lancy Laboratories - Electroplating Industry - $189,200 (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Contracts - Lawler, Matusky & Skelly - Environmental Water Sites - $103,460 (Box 10, Folder 407)
  - Contracts - Lawler, Matusky & Skelly Eng. - Hudson - Env. Site - $69,700 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    See note on lawsuit in "Lawler" file.
  - Contracts - Linton, Mields & Coston - Overall Study - Contract WQ3AC002: $36,000 - Contract WQ4AC008: $78,000 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Contracts - Lockwood Greene - (Textile Industry Study) - $171,895 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Contracts - Management Sciences Systems - Analysis of Agricultural Impact Studies - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Contracts - Masselli, Joseph W. - Consultant, Textiles - $2,800 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - Contracts - Arthur G. McGee, Cleveland, Iron & Steel - $220,000 (Box 10, Folder 413)
  - Contracts - Meta Systems Inc. - Economic Impact - Municipal Effluents - $120,000 (Box 10, Folder 414)
  - Contracts - Meta Systems Inc. - Environmental Water Sites - $46,566 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - Contracts - Metcalf & Eddy - (Municipal Technology Study) - $498,726 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Contracts - Midwest Research Institute - Environmental Water Site - $72,500 (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Contracts - Midwest Research Institute - Non-point Sources - $35,000 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Contracts - Miller, Perry - Consultant - Institutional "Doers" - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Contracts - National Academy of Sciences - $489,000 (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Contracts - NBER (National Bureau of Economic Research) - Commission Approved June 6, 1974 - $379,400 (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - Contracts - National Planning Association - Economic Impact - Selected Mfg. - $89,000 (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Contracts - National Planning Association - Economics: Recreation - $192,500 (Box 11, Folder 423)
  - Contracts - North Star Research & Development Institute - Environmental Water Site - $80,300 (Box 11, Folder 424)
  - Contracts - Oregon Research Institute - Institutional: Attitudes - $119,400 (Box 11, Folder 425)
  - Contracts - Parametrix, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $69,130 (Box 11, Folder 426)
  - Contracts - Price, Victoria - Consultant - Institutional: "Doers" - $10,000 (Box 11, Folder 427)
  - Contracts - Process Research, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $68,965 (Box 11, Folder 428)
  - Contracts - Procon - (Synthetics and Plastics Study) - $171,254 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  - Contracts - PIEC (Public Interest Economics Center) - $28,790 (Box 11, Folder 430)
  - Contracts - Public Research Institute (Center for Naval Analyses) - Economic Impact - International Trade - $115,000 (Box 11, Folder 431)
  - Contracts - Ragan (James) Associates - Institutional: Public Participation - $78,195 (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Contracts - Resources for the Future - $7,500 (Box 11, Folder 433)
  - Contracts - Seneca, Joseph J. - Consultant - $5,000 (Box 11, Folder 434)
  - Contracts - Smith, Dr. V. Kerry - Consultant - $7,500 (Box 11, Folder 435)
  - Contracts - Southern California Coastal Water Research Project - $19,400 (Box 11, Folder 436)
  - Contracts - Stevens, Thompson & Runyan, Inc. - River Basin: Yellowstone - $200,000 (Box 11, Folder 437)
  - Contracts - Stevens, Thompson & Runyan, Inc. - River Basin: Puget Sound-Lake Washington - $215,000 (Box 11, Folder 438)
  - Contracts - Teknekron - Steam Electric Power - $262,000 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Contracts - TetraTech Inc. - Environmental Water Sites - $311,935 (Box 11, Folder 440)
  - Contracts - Tippetts-Abbett-McCarthy-Stratton (General Clarke) - $197,000 (Box 11, Folder 441)
  - Contracts - Touche Ross & Co. - Institutional: Construction Grants - $149,000 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  - Contracts - Toups Corp. - Irrigation Return Flows - $75,000 (Box 11, Folder 443)
  - Contracts - TRW, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $49,400 (Box 11, Folder 444)
  - Contracts - University of Texas, Austin (Dale Wittington, Consultant) - $6,400 (Box 11, Folder 445)
  - Contracts - Urban Systems Research & Engineering, Cambridge, MA - Economic Impact - Direct Economic Incidence - $91,400 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  - Contracts - Utah State University Foundation - River Basin: Colorado - $225,000 (Box 11, Folder 447)
  - Contracts - University of Virginia - Economic: Computer - INFORUM and CONSAD - $10,000 (Box 11, Folder 448)
  - Contracts - Vanderbilt University - Environmental Site: Percy Priest Reservoir - $50,000 (Box 11, Folder 449)
  - Contracts - Virginia Institute of Marine Science - Environmental Water Site: Chesapeake Bay - $59,100 (Box 11, Folder 450)
  - Contracts - Water Purification Associates - Innovative Technologies - $65,000 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    Contains transcript of proceedings of National Commission on Water Quality meeting of June 6, 1974.
  - Contracts - Water Resources Engineers - Environmental Water Sites - $170,335 (Box 11, Folder 452)
  - Contracts - Whitman, Dr. Ira L. - Institutional: Construction Grants & Permits - $2,000 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - Contracts - Whitman, Dr. Ira L. - Regional: Evaluation of Ohio & Kanawha - $3,000 (Box 11, Folder 454)
  - Contracts - Wise, Harold F. - Institutional: Planning - $106,294 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Contracts - Alphabetical List (Box 11, Folder 456)
  - Contracts - Numerical Order - Costs (Box 11, Folder 457)
  - Contracts - General (Box 11, Folder 458)
  - Contracts - Contractor Reports - Publication Policy (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Contracts - Publications List (Box 11, Folder 460)
    Note: Also lists reports not published.
  - Contracts - Contractor Reports - NTIS Publication (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Contracts - Administrative Procedures for Handling (Box 11, Folder 462)
    See Box #2 for consultant and contractor selection procedures.
  - Contracts - Contract Disputes - Procedures (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Contracts - Deobligations (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Contracts - Contract Releases (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Contracts - Consultants (Program & Executive Directors Authority) (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - Contracts - Contract Increases - Executive Director's Authority (discretionary) (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Contracts - Contractor Invoices Paid After April 16, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Contracts - Contract Costs - By Program Area (Ref: Contract Inventory, July 1976) (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - Contracts - Modifications (overall) (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Contracts - Overall Overruns (Box 11, Folder 471)
    See individual contractor files for specific cases.
  - Contracts - Status Reports (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - Contracts - Status of Reports, August 1975 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - Contracts - Inventory & Status, June 30, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - Contracts - Reports Stored at Interior Department (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Contracts - Status (during "budget crisis"), February 1976 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - Industries - Costs, McGraw-Hill Survey, May 1974, 1975, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - Industries - General, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - Industries - Chemical, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Industries - Iron & Steel, 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Industries - Iron & Steel - Mahoning Valley, Ohio, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - Industries - Mining, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - Industries - Petroleum Refining, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - Industries - Pulp and Paper, 1972, 1974, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 484)
  - Industries - Pulp and Paper, Ketchikan, Alaska, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 485)
  - Industries - Steam Electric Power, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 486)
  - Industries - Comments from Outside Groups: Procedure and Index (Box 12, Folder 487)
  - Industries - Domestic Council Task Force Report, October 1975 (Box 12, Folder 488)
  - Industries - Dr. Gee: Caption Summaries on Contract (Box 12, Folder 489)
  - Industries - Iron and Steel - McKee - Comments (Box 12, Folder 490)
  - Industries - Organic Chemicals - Catalytic - Comments (Box 12, Folder 491)
  - Industries - Inorganic Chemicals - Catalytic - Comments (Box 12, Folder 492)
  - Industries - Petroleum Refining - Engineering Science - Comments (Box 12, Folder 493)
  - Industries - Pulp and Paper - Hazen and Sawyer - Comments (Box 12, Folder 494)
  - Industries - Electroplating - Metal Finishing - Lancy - Comments (Box 12, Folder 495)
  - Industries - Metal Finishing - Assessment of NBER Report (H. Cook paper April 9, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 496)
  - Industries - Canned & Preserved Fruits & Vegetables - Environmental Associates - Comments (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - Industries - Technology - Procon - (Plastics and Synthetics) - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 498)
  - Industries - Textiles - Lockwood Green - Comments (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - Industries - Steam Electric Power (Technology) - Teknekron - Comments (Box 12, Folder 500)
  - Industries - Technology: Water Purification - Innovative Technologies - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 501)
  - Industries - Technology: American Public Works - Needs Survey - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - Industries - Technology: Metcalf and Eddy - (Publicly Owned Treatment Works) - Comments on Draft Reports (Box 12, Folder 503)
  - Industries - Urban Runoff - Black, Crow & Eidsness - Comments (Box 12, Folder 504)
  - Industries - Construction Grants - Institutional - Touche Ross - Comments (Box 12, Folder 505)
  - Industries - Enforcement - Institutional Environmental Law Institute - Comments (Box 12, Folder 506)
  - Industries - Permit Program - Institutional - Energy & Environmental Analysis - Comments (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - Industries - Permit Program - Contract Report Assessment (H. Cook paper July 17, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 508)
  - Industries - Public Participation - Institutional - James Ragan Associates - Comments (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - Industries - Regional: ABT Associates (Merrimack-Nashua) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - Industries - Regional: Stevens, Thompson & Runyan (Puget Sound) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - Industries - Regional: Houston Ship Channel (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Industries - Regional: Betz Environmental Engineers (Delaware River Basin) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Industries - Regional: Stevens, Thompson & Runyan (Yellowstone) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - Industries - Regional: Dalton, Dalton, Little & Newport (Lake Erie) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Industries - Lake Erie - Contractor Report Assessment (H. Cook paper June 14, 1975) (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Industries - Economics: Public Research Institute (Limitations on Foreign Trade) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - Industries - Economics: NBER (Pulp and Paper) - Comments (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Industries - Economics: DPRA (Feedlots) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 519)
  - Industries - Economics: Battelle Memorial (Increased Swimming) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 520)
  - Industries - Economics: Florida State University (Commercial Fisheries) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 521)
  - Industries - Economics: Meta Systems (Municipal Options) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 522)
  - Industries - Economics: The Conference Board (5 Pilot Studies) - Comments (Box 13, Folder 523)
  - Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number One) (Box 13, Folder 524)
  - Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number Two) (Box 13, Folder 525)
  - Industries - General Industry Studies: Battelle Memorial (Categories 1-38) - Comments on Draft Contractor Reports (Number Three) (Box 13, Folder 526)
  - Industries - Outside Groups - New York State (Box 13, Folder 527)
    Response to NAR letters to industry, states, cities and environmental groups.
  - Industries - NAR Letter December 13, 1974 with Digest of Responses (Box 13, Folder 528)
  - Industries - Industry - Associated Industries of Alabama (Box 13, Folder 529)
  - Industries - Industry Comments: Canned Food & Vegetable Processing, NAR Letter December 13, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 530)
  - Industry Comments - Chambers of Commerce (Box 13, Folder 531)
  - Industry Comments - Chemical Processes (Box 13, Folder 532)
  - Industry Comments - Dairy Products (Box 13, Folder 533)
  - Industry Comments - Electroplating (Box 13, Folder 534)
  - Industry Comments - Fertilizers (Box 13, Folder 535)
  - Industry Comments - Forestry & Timber Products (Box 13, Folder 536)
  - Industry Comments - Glass Manufacturing (Box 13, Folder 537)
  - Industry Comments - Iron & Steel (Box 13, Folder 538)
  - Industry Comments - Meats & Poultry (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - Industry Comments - Mining (Box 13, Folder 540)
  - Industry Comments - Miscellaneous Industries (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Industry Comments - Nonferrous Metals (Box 13, Folder 542)
  - Industry Comments - Petroleum (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - Industry Comments - Pulp & Paper (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - Industry Comments - Rubber (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - Industry Comments - Steam Electric Power (Box 13, Folder 546)
  - Industry Comments - Textiles (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - Industry Comments - Transportation (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - Industry Comments - Water Conditioning (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - Industry Comments - NAR Letter October 24, 1974, with Digest of Responses (Box 13, Folder 550)
  - Industry Comments - Governors' Responses to NAR Letter of October 24, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - Industry Comments - Cities: NAR Letter, 3rd Week of August 1974, with Digest of Comments Received (Box 13, Folder 552)
  - Industry Comments - Cities: Responses to NAR Letter, August 1974 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Industry Comments - Environmentalists: NAR Letter of April 7, 1974 with Digest Highlights (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (1) (Box 13, Folder 555)
  - Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (2) (Box 13, Folder 556)
  - Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (3) (Box 14, Folder 557)
  - Industry Comments - Environmentalists' Responses to NAR Letter, April 7, 1974 (4) (Box 14, Folder 558)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Outlines, November 9, 1973 - June 17, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 559)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Preamble - May 8, 1975 Through Final Report (Box 14, Folder 560)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Background - July 31, 1974 Through First Staff Draft (Box 14, Folder 561)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Background, September 2, 1975 - December 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 562)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - First Staff Draft - Public Release / Participation, September 2, 1975 - December 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 563)
  - Reports - "Opinions" Paper of Program Staff/Commission by Joe Moore, July 31, 1975 and August 8, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    i.e., staff conclusions
  - Reports - Procedure for Completion (Box 14, Folder 565)
  - Reports - Recommendations / Options / Issues Papers Prepared by Clarke, September 8, 1975 - December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    One paper by Moore
  - Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (1), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 567)
    Originally called "Synthesis" and "Discussion Document."
  - Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (2), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 568)
  - Reports - Chapter I: Issues and Findings - Drafts (3), September 9, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 569)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Benefits & Health Controversy (Box 14, Folder 570)
  - Reports - Costs of Treatment / Capital Requirements (Box 14, Folder 571)
  - Reports - Cook Paper, "Major Questions", October 10, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - Reports - Cook Paper, "National Water Commission Experience", November 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 573)
  - Reports - Cook Paper, "Catch-up Period", February 18, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 574)
  - Reports - Cook Paper, "Report: Proposed Format" (Box 14, Folder 575)
    Used as basis for Chairman's "Separate Views" in Commission Report.
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafting Through First Staff Draft of September 2, 1975 (General) (Box 14, Folder 576)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Technology - (Staff Drafts to September 2, 1975) (General) (Box 14, Folder 577)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Industrial - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 14, Folder 578)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Municipal - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 14, Folder 579)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Tech/Agricultural - Non-point & Innovative (Box 14, Folder 580)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Economic & Social - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Economic & Social - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Environmental - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 583)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Environmental - (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 584)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Institutional - (Staff Drafts Up to September 15, 1975) (1) (Box 15, Folder 585)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Institutional - (Staff Drafts Up to September 15, 1975) (2) (Box 15, Folder 586)
  - Reports - Staff/Commission - Drafts: Regional- (Staff Drafts Up to September 2, 1975) (Box 15, Folder 587)
  - Reports - First Staff Draft - "Partial"; Preliminary 1 of 3: Technology Chapter, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 588)
  - Reports - First Staff Draft - "Partial"; Preliminary 2 of 3: Economic Impacts, September 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 589)